away from my
bestie after
years
of supporting
her
through a
mental
health
crisis.
Am I the
a hole for
wanting to drop
my best friend
of three years?
So boom, I'm
F-16 and I'm
in a current
friendship with
my
best friend.
I'll call her
A. We've known
each other
since
seventh grade
and
we dated during
that time
which
ended
horribly.
In that
relationship,
it
was very
emotionally
draining
because of
how she
would hurt
H-E-R-S-E-L-F
and
almost
O-D.
Now fast
forwarding to
Valentine's,
we're
not friends
A-T-M, this
girl comes
up to
we're going to
call her Abby.
She comes and
gives me a
letter saying a
wanted me to
give you this.
Mind you I'm
already having
a
bad day because
of family
issues
that happened
on
Valentine's
Day two
years ago.
In this
letter, it's
all this
hateful stuff
she said
and how
much she
That day
I went
into the
bathroom and
cried for
Now we're
into eighth
grade and
she apologizes
to me
which I
forget her
but never
We've been
friends
since then but
he mental
health
was bad since
the day I
met her.
What really got
worse was in
Sophomore year,
she'd
been posting
stuff
on Twitter
tagging
a certain
community
which I feel
like she
shouldn't
be in and
posted her
Iqwa.
We went to
the admin about
it, showed
screenshots
and more.
She got sent
to the mental
hospital for
two
weeks.
Now it's
towards
the end of
Sophomore year
and
she randomly
comes
up to me
crying saying
if I hate
her and stuff.
I asked where'd
she get that
from and told
me Abby told
her that Abby
is having
fallouts
with her
friends during
this time
and SM
more stuff
happening.
I go to
the bathroom
and
crawl
underneath the
stall on that
dirty, nasty
floor
and console
her.
Once we got
her out of
there and
talked
to the admin,
we head into
class.
30 minutes
later,
she's back at
talking to that
same girl about
if she wanting
to smoke
or something
later after
I said
you shouldn't
hang out
That was my
breaking point.
Over the
summer, I
barely talked
to her
until
volleyball
tryouts, she
didn't make
Now entering
junior
year, it just
started and
Iqqq
if I have
the mental
capacity
to deal
with that
anymore.
I'm tired
of this
bullshit app.
We barely talk
now
and even at
lunch
when we sit
together
and she thinks
I'm
mad at
her but I
told her I'm
not.
I hate
confrontation
BTW
and just
didn't want
to continue
that
conversation.
I think I've
just
grown out of
that
friendship and
don't know
what to do.
Oh and
she likes
to gaslight
me and
others a
Am I in
the wrong or
no because I
don't think I'm
selfish for
thinking
I really need
people
to tell me that
I'm not being
crazy
for wanting to
drop
her.